Go... go left, left! Yes, yes, yes!
Go... go left, go left!
I can't believe I got that kill!
Nice, nice, nice!
You're a pro! Ah, I'm dead, I'm dead!
Pro!
What a pro! Pro, pro!
Then you watch his back, he watches yours.
Otherwise, on your own...
you definitely can't cover it all, right?
Anyway, it's really not hard. Not hard at all.
Lin Ran.
There are some...
And another thing is...
Lin Ran, um...
between two people...
Lin Ran!
Come home with me.
Attention, please.
The user at terminal 18 has logged off.
Please clean up the desk promptly.
Look at the state of you.
Let's go.
A date?
Yeah, don't you want to?
Of course I want to.
It's just...
I haven't thought it through.
Then think about it some more.
Where are you going?
To the bathroom.
Alright.
What are you all doing?
Are you crazy?
Yeah, how can we make decisions for her?
Why can't we?
We're the same person anyway.
Have you forgotten a lesson from the past?
What lesson from the past?
Fine, playing dumb, huh?
Isn't this pretty cool?
Okay, when you went shopping yesterday,
weren't you looking at that dress?
That's right, it looks pretty good.
It does look pretty good.
I'll buy it for you, it's fine.
We're easygoing.
The two of us don't mind.
But Lin Ran, because of this,
cried her eyes out.
Yeah, a tattoo can still be removed.
But choosing the wrong partner is serious.
Are you guys overthinking this?
I wasn't really deciding for Lin Ran.
I just wanted to
check him out for her.
You better take responsibility.
Alright.
Stop nagging.
If anything goes wrong, it's on me.
Don't follow me.
What took you so long?
I told you I went to the bathroom.
So,
were you serious about going on a date?
Of course.
Great.
Where do you want to go?
Uncle! Uncle!
Where are you going?
I want to go too.
Stop fooling around.
I just want to cause trouble!
I want to go!
Why don't you bring her along?
No, no, no need.
I'll take Xiaomei back first.
Unless you buy me another ice cream.
Okay.
Alright, I'll send you an address later.
We can meet up there.
Okay.
Thanks.
Bye-bye.
See you in a bit.
So this is the date spot you mentioned.
What, you don't like it?
N-No, it's not that.
I'm just a bit surprised.
Aren't we going?
What's on your mind?
Nothing.
Let's go.
Are you happy?
I am.
I knew you'd come.
By the way,
this is the substitute I told you about.
David.
Let's skip the small talk.
I have a flight to catch.
Let's get right to it.
David, this game is one or the other.
I'm rooting for you.
Okay.
Lin.
What are you guys doing?
Playing a game.
You play video games?
There's a lot I can do.
So you're playing against him?
Come on, come on!
All right, let's get started then.
You got this!
Don't embarrass yourself.
Show them what you've got.
Stop hissing.
It's just a draw.
Yeah, you'll definitely win.
I wouldn't be so sure.
If you lose,
don't ever brag about
how good you are at gaming.
That's never gonna happen.
Champion
Champion, come here.
Champion. Champion.
Congrats on qualifying for the team.
Thank you.
But... I can't join your team anymore.
Why?
Because I feel like...
this goes against why I started gaming.
The reason I like gaming
is that I don't want to be tied down.
But once a hobby becomes a career,
it's just not the same anymore.
Okay.
Then I respect your decision.
Anyway, if you figure things out later,
or change your mind,
come find me anytime.
I'm off.
See ya.
What? You want to talk me out of it too?
Not at all.
I think you make perfect sense.
Then why are you looking at me?
Can I play a couple rounds with you?
Bring it on. Who's afraid?
Don't go easy on me.
Wait a sec.
Here. No, no, no! Don't move, don't move!
Take this! I'm not waiting!
I... I haven't used my ultimate yet!
Hit, hit, hit!
Take this! No waiting, no waiting!
Uppercut!
My bad. Why can't I use my ultimate?
Wait, wait! I used it!
I used it!
Wait, wait!
Fire!
Wow...
I can't beat you at all.
It'd be a miracle if you could.
One more round.
You're on.
Let's switch characters.
My time is up.
What do you mean?
The rest of the time is yours.
You really are strict about this.
Why? Don't you need the time?
Well...
It's not that I don't need it.
What's wrong?
Let's go to the next date spot.
Sure.
Is this your hobby too?
Why, is it not allowed?
It's not that you can't.
It's just a bit of a contrast...
And you are...?
I'm a competitor.
Name?
Lin Ran.
Found it.
But your match isn't until later.
I want to warm up first.
But you're way too early.
Is that okay?
I suppose so.
But you need to finish before three.
The afternoon matches will start then.
No problem.
Let's go. Don't just stand there.
Go get changed.
Go, hurry up.
Done changing. Come on.
Here, give it a try.
No need.
I used to practice a lot in college.
Not bad.
How about
we have a match?
No problem.
Are you ready?
Ready.
Begin!
Here.
You could at least go easy on him.
It's your first date.
Don't hurt his ego.
When you play games,
I don't see you caring about his ego.
It's a competition.
You have to take it seriously, right?
You lost.
Thanks.
But among amateurs,
I'm pretty good, right?
Among amateurs, you're average at best.
You call this average?
Yeah, very average.
Alright, I'm just kidding.
You're really good.
Come on.
The real match starts now.
Wait.
Isn't it already over?
That was just a warm up.
Let's go, let's go.
Why do I feel like Lin Ran
is starting to like that guy?
What about you?
Do you like him?
I wouldn't say I like him,
but I don't hate him either.
Can you handle this?
Yeah.
This is the real match.
Come on.
Speed it up.
Go.
So have you made a decision?
What decision?
To give the time to Lin Ran.